{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","address":"15 E Kirby St., Suite D","zipcode":"48202","owner":"S.Levine/Right Handed LeftyLLC","licenseNumber":"083441","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/27/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000741613543AC454C0D870B9B0242E4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43794","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","inspectionDate":"2018-10-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"133","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43794","inspectionDate":"10/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"inspectionid":"43794","inspectionDate":"10/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"EXPIRED DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"43794","inspectionDate":"10/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Hand-drying towels","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"43794","inspectionDate":"10/17/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"41933","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","inspectionDate":"2018-03-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41933","inspectionDate":"3/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"inspectionid":"41933","inspectionDate":"3/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"3-306.11","violationDescription":"Except for nuts in the shell and whole, raw fruits and vegetables that are intended for hulling, peeling, or washing by the CONSUMER before consumption, FOOD on display shall be protected from contamination by the use of PACKAGING; counter, service line, or salad bar FOOD guards; display cases; or other effective means. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food on display","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lacking protection","subProblem":"Sneeze guards","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Counter(s)","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"},{"inspectionid":"41933","inspectionDate":"3/20/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"3-307.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination that may result from a factor or source not specified under Subparts 3-301 - 3-306.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not protected","subProblem":"From contamination","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"}]},{"inspectionid":"39766","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","inspectionDate":"2017-08-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"39766","inspectionDate":"8/29/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"3-307.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination that may result from a factor or source not specified under Subparts 3-301 - 3-306.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not protected","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in protected manner."},{"inspectionid":"39766","inspectionDate":"8/29/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"inspectionid":"39766","inspectionDate":"8/29/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"3-306.11","violationDescription":"Except for nuts in the shell and whole, raw fruits and vegetables that are intended for hulling, peeling, or washing by the CONSUMER before consumption, FOOD on display shall be protected from contamination by the use of PACKAGING; counter, service line, or salad bar FOOD guards; display cases; or other effective means. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food on display","subItem":"display table","problemDescription":"Lacking protection","subProblem":"Sneeze guards","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Lack of Sneeze Guard","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"}]},{"inspectionid":"37679","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","inspectionDate":"2017-01-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"4","pfcount":"1","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"5","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37679","inspectionDate":"1/18/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 100 ppm","subProblem":"And/or water temperature below 120 degrees f","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Dishwasher","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"inspectionid":"37679","inspectionDate":"1/18/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"EXPIRED DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-01-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"37679","inspectionDate":"1/18/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"3-306.11","violationDescription":"Except for nuts in the shell and whole, raw fruits and vegetables that are intended for hulling, peeling, or washing by the CONSUMER before consumption, FOOD on display shall be protected from contamination by the use of PACKAGING; counter, service line, or salad bar FOOD guards; display cases; or other effective means. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food on display","subItem":"display table","problemDescription":"Lacking protection","subProblem":"Other effective means","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Lack of Sneeze Guard","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"},{"inspectionid":"37679","inspectionDate":"1/18/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"4-501.110","violationDescription":"(A) The temperature of the wash solution in spray type warewashers that use hot water to SANITIZERS may not be less than:     \r\n(1) For a stationary rack, single temperature machine, 74°C (165°F);(Pf)   \r\n(2) For a stationary rack, dual temperature machine, 66°C (150°F); (Pf)   \r\n(3) For a single tank, conveyor, dual temperature machine, 71°C (160°F);(Pf) or\r\n(4) For a multitank, conveyor, multitemperature machine, 66°C (150°F).(Pf)  \r\n(B) The temperature of the wash solution in spray-type warewashers that use chemicals to SANITIZE may not be less than 49°C (120°F). (Pf)","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Dish machine wash solution temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 120 degrees F","subProblem":"For chemical sanitizing machine","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Dishwasher","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"inspectionid":"37679","inspectionDate":"1/18/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Sink","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"Lack of AIR GAP","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-01-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."}]},{"inspectionid":"36447","establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","inspectionDate":"2016-09-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5011"}}